So, what's new Mark? How is your new job going?
To be honest, I can't complain. I really love the company that I am working for.
My co-workers are all really friendly and helpful. They really help me feel welcome.
It's a really energetic and fun atmosphere. My boss is hilarious and he's really flexible.
Really? How so?
He allows me to come in when I want and make my own hours.
I can also leave early if I start early. There is no real dress code either.
I can wear jeans and a t-shirt if I want. I can even wear shorts in the summer.
Wow. It sounds really cool. I can't stand wearing a suit every day.
Which do you prefer? Working late or finishing early?
I prefer finishing early. I really enjoy the morning. I love getting up early and going for a run.
There is nothing like watching the sunrise while drinking my morning coffee.
Really? I am opposite. I love sleeping in.
I am most alert in the evenings. I'm a real night owl.
Well, you know what they say. The early bird catches the worm.
You know, you could be right. Maybe I will try to go to bed a little earlier tonight.